Richard Rodgers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Miscellaneous Sketches (Box 20)
  - [M.S. 5], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "[You are so lovely and I'm so lonely]" (sung in Something Gay, 1935), "[As though you were there]" (cut from Heads Up!, 1929) (Box-folder 20/4)
  - [M.S. 6], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: "Now I believe" (became "Isn't it romantic?" from Love Me Tonight, 1932), "Hands" (probably cut from America's Sweetheart, 1931) (Box-folder 20/4)
  - [M.S. 7], Holograph sketches in pencil; [12] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "[I'm a] queen [in my own domain]" (cut from Hollywood Party, 1934) p. [2]: "Verse [Keep away from the] moonlight" (cut from Hollywood Party, 1934) p. [3]: "[That's the] r[h]ythm of the day" (from Dancing Lady, 1933) p. [4]: "Verse Dancing lady" (from Dancing Lady, 1933), "Verse Door is open," "[That's the] r[h]ythm of the day" (from Dancing Lady, 1933) p. [5]: "D[ancing] l[ady]" (from Dancing Lady, 1933) [partial page] p. [6]: "Tomorrow's Sunday" p. [8]: "Verse Be a star" p. [9]: "Reincarnation" (from Hollywood Party, 1934) p. [10]: "Verse [That's the] r[h]ythm [of the day" (from Dancing Lady, 1933), "H[ollywood] P[arty]" (from Hollywood Party, 1934) (Box-folder 20/5)
  - [M.S. 8], Holograph sketches in pencil; [3] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "Easy to remember" (from Mississippi, 1935) p. [2]: "[Please] make me be good" (from Let's Have Fun, 1935), "[I'll take a little of] you on toast" (from Let's Have Fun, 1935) (Box-folder 20/6)
  - [M.S. 9], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "When your love lets you down" (became "There's a small hotel" which was cut from Jumbo, 1935, and used in On Your Toes, 1936) p. [2]: "Slaughter on Tenth Avenue" (from On Your Toes, 1936) (Box-folder 20/6)
  - [M.S. 10], Holograph sketches in pencil; [4] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "The circus comes to town" p. [2]: "Patter opening," "[Too good for the] average man" (from On Your Toes, 1936) p. [3]: "Verse [Glad to be] unhappy" (from On Your Toes, 1936), "Opening," "Refrain" p. [4]: "Verse Are you my love[?]" (from Dancing Pirate, 1936) (Box-folder 20/7)
  - [M.S. 11], Holograph sketches in pencil; [4] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "Solitaire" p. [2]: "Ballet," "Verse Who are you" (from the film version of The Boys from Syracuse, 1940) p. [4]: "Verse [A] barking baby [never bites]" (from Higher and Higher, 1940), "[Disgustingly] rich" (from Higher and Higher, 1940) (Box-folder 20/7)
  - [M.S. 12], Holograph sketches in pencil; [10] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "Carretero"[sic](from They Met in Argentina, 1941), "Cowboy" p. [2]: "Trio Ranchero," "Contrapunto" (from They Met in Argentina, 1941), "New end for 'Best of me'" p. [3]: "Chaco" p. [4]: "Plant you now, [dig you later]" (from Pal Joey, 1940), "Sung in a parlor," "[Maiden?] now" p. [5]: "Tango" p. [7]: "Show," "Bewitched, bothered and bewildered" (from Pal Joey, 1940), "Alter[nate] middle," "[Bewitched, bothered and bewildered: verse]" (from Pal Joey, 1940) p. [8]: "[Take him]" (from Pal Joey, 1940), "Lullaby?" p. [9]: "Ranchero," "Verse Simpatica" (from They Met in Argentina, 1941) p. [10]: "On the track: verse" (from They Met in Argentina, 1941), "N[orth] A[merica] meets S[outh] A[merica]" (from They Met in Argentina, 1941) (Box-folder 20/8)
  - [M.S. 13], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "1st love dance," "When the willow blooms," "Dressing the girl" p. [2]: "Festive dance" (Box-folder 20/9)
  - [M.S. 14], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "Go west," "Soldiers," "College girls" p. [2]: "Honeymoon," "Hurry" (Box-folder 20/9)
  - [Unidentified sketches], Holograph sketches in pencil; [13] leaves (Box-folder 20/10)
  - [Unidentified lyric sketches], Holograph lyric sketches in pencil & ink; [9] p. (Box-folder 20/11)
- Photographs (Box 20-21)
  The Photographs are contained in three folders. They span the years 1920-1979.
  Arrangement is chronological.
  - [Camp Paradox - 1920]: Photograph of "The Faculty/1920," black & white; 9 1/4" x 7" See also: [Camp Paradox materials] in MISCELLANEOUS (Box-folder 20/12)
  - [ca. 1920-1947, 1953]: Photographs (10) in black & white; 8" x 10" (Box-folder 21/1)
  - [1955-1965]: Photographs (8), 6 in black & white and 2 in color; 8" x 10" (Box-folder 21/2)
  - [1976-1979, n.d.]: Photographs (9) in black & white; 8" x 10" (Box-folder 21/3)
- Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  The Miscellaneous series contains Camp Paradox materials, Carbon copies of correspondence with the Library of Congress (1964, 1965), a typed lists of the items in the collection, Memorbilia, and related items from Richard Rodgers 65th birthday tribute.
  Arrangement is by folder heading.
  - [Camp Paradox materials]: "The Paradoxian," published at Camp Paradox, N.Y., some autographed; 7 issues (1918-1920, 1925) See also: Paradox victory song/chant in NON-SHOW MUSIC (Box-folder 21/4)
  - [Camp Paradox materials]: "Camp Paradox 1914" (informational booklet) See also: Paradox victory song/chant in NON-SHOW MUSIC (Box-folder 21/4)
  - [Letter]: Carbon of typed letter (Eileen Minich to Harold Glick, 5/17/65) re original Rodgers' mss. sent to the Library of Congress (Box-folder 21/5)
  - [Letter]: Carbon of typed letter (9/1/64) describing mss. sent via letter above (Box-folder 21/5)
  - [List re contents of Richard Rodgers Collection]: Typed lists (2); 18 p. each (Box-folder 21/6)
  - [Memorabilia]: Invitation to Richard Rodgers exhibition at Hallmark Gallery, N.Y., 9/19/72 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - [Memorabilia]: Keepsake from the event honoring Richard Rodgers at the Library of Congress, 6/4/80 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - [Memorabilia]: Autographed guest list, 6/4/80 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - [65th birthday tribute to Richard Rodgers]: Press release re tribute to Rodgers, 6/28/67; 2 p. (Box-folder 21/8)
  - [65th birthday tribute to Richard Rodgers]: Commemorative linen napkin of the song "Sweet sixty-five" (from I'd Rather Be Right, 1937) (Box-folder 21/8)
  - [65th birthday tribute to Richard Rodgers]: Envelope (oversize) (Box-folder 21/8)
Appendix: Song Titles
Aida NON-SHOW MUSIC
All at once Babes in Arms
All at once you love her Pipe Dream
All dark people Babes in Arms
All er nothin! Oklahoma!
All I owe Ioway State Fair
All kinds of people Pipe Dream
All Points West! NON-SHOW MUSIC
Allegro Allegro
Allez-up! The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Amarillo They Met in Argentina
American beauty rose The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
American rifle, The The Valiant Years
Angel without wings I Married an Angel
Animated objects I Married an Angel
Anna's bedroom The King and I
Anytime, anywhere, anyhow June Days
April fool The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Arab friend Lawrence of Arabia
Arab military Lawrence of Arabia
Are you my love? MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 10]
As far as I'm concerned Two by Two
As once I loved you Rex
As though you were there Heads Up!
Atlantic blues Lido Lady
Away from home State Fair
Away from you Rex
Baby you love, The Me and Juliet
Baby's awake now Spring Is Here
Back to nature The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Bad news Too Many Girls
Bali ha'i South Pacific
Band of the ne'er-do-wells, The If I Were King
Bargaining Do I Hear a Waltz?
Barking baby never bites, A Higher and Higher
Be my host No Strings
Beauty contest, The Ever Green
Beauty of another day, The Lido Lady
Beauty sequence I'd Rather Be Right
Because we're young Follow Thru
Beneath the southern cross Victory at Sea
Better be good to me MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Bewitched, bothered and bewildered Pal Joey
Big black giant, The Me and Juliet
Big brother The Boys from Syracuse
Birds on high Betsy
Black diamond Hollywood Party
Bloody Mary South Pacific
Blow high, blow low Carousel
Blue Monday Higher and Higher
Blue ocean blues MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
Blue room, The The Girl Friend
Bob-o-link Temple Bells
Bombardier song, The NON-SHOW MUSIC
Boys and girls like you and me Oklahoma!
Bright canary yellow South Pacific
British military & music hall Lawrence of Arabia
Brother department, The Two by Two
Bugle blow Betsy
Building up theme Victory at Sea
Bum's opera Pipe Dream
Bumper found a grand Hallelujah, I'm a Bum
Burning Hollywood Party
But the days on a planet Allegro
Bye and bye Dearest Enemy
Can't you do a friend a favor A Connecticut Yankee
Carefree careterro They Met in Argentina
Careless rhapsody By Jupiter
Carousel waltz Carousel
Carriers Victory at Sea
Cause we got cake Ghost Town
Cause we got cake Too Many Girls
Cette heure NON-SHOW MUSIC
Charming, charming Peggy-Ann
Chase, The Rex
Chicago Pal Joey
Chop suey Flower Drum Song
Christmas at Hampton Court Rex
Chuck it! Peggy-Ann
Chuck it! Lido Lady
Church, The The Valiant Years
Churchill is determined The Valiant Years
Cinderella Higher and Higher
Circus is on parade, The Jumbo
Circus wedding, The Jumbo
Clementine NON-SHOW MUSIC
Clementine NON-SHOW MUSIC
Climb ev'ry mountain The Sound of Music
Cockeyed optimist, A South Pacific
College Baby! Bad Habits of 1925
Colour of her eyes, The MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Colour of her eyes, The Ever Green
Come back to me I Picked a Daisy
Come home Allegro
Come to court Rex
Come with me The Boys from Syracuse
Comfort me Winkle Town
Contrapunto They Met in Argentina
Courtly etiquette If I Were King
Covenant, The Two by Two
Crazy elbows MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Creole crooning song The Girl Friend
Cup of tea, A Lido Lady
Cup of tea, A Spring Is Here
Cutting the cane They Met in Argentina
Damsel who done all the dirt, The The Girl Friend
Dancing lady MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 7]
Dancing lady Hollywood Party
Dancing on the ceiling Ever Green
Dancing on the ceiling Simple Simon
Danse grotesque à la nègre One Dam Thing After Another
Day Sven Gundersen died, The I Remember Mama
Dear friend NON-SHOW MUSIC
Dear Jane Rex
Dear old Syracuse The Boys from Syracuse
Death and debris Victory at Sea
Deep sea The Valiant Years
Den of iniquity Pal Joey
Diavolo Jumbo
Disgustingly rich Higher and Higher
Dites-moi South Pacific
Do I hear a waltz? Do I Hear a Waltz?
Do I hear you saying, "I love you"? MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Do I love you because you're beautiful? Cinderella
Do it the hard way Pal Joey
Do-re-mi The Sound of Music
Doing a little clog dance Ever Green
Don't be afraid of an animal Androcles and the Lion
Don't come to court Rex
Don't laugh at Trina I Remember Mama
Don't marry me Flower Drum Song
Don't tell your folks Simple Simon
Down by the river Mississippi
Down by the sea MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Down on the Bahamas NON-SHOW MUSIC
Dresden Sonata, The NON-SHOW MUSIC
Dummy march Betsy
Dutch Treat Club, The NON-SHOW MUSIC
Eager beaver No Strings
Easy come, easy go I Remember Mama
Easy to remember MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 8]
Edelweiss The Sound of Music
Election, The One Dam Thing After Another
Elizabeth Rex
Emperor's thumb, The Androcles and the Lion
England at play The Valiant Years
Eternal stars Rex
Ev'ry day (comes something beautiful) I Remember Mama
Ev'ry Sunday afternoon Higher and Higher
Ev'rybody's got a home but me Pipe Dream
Ev'rything that's gonna be has been Two by Two
Ever-ready Freddy Lido Lady
Everybody loves Leona Do I Hear a Waltz?
Everybody loves you Fools for Scandal
Everybody loves you I'd Rather Be Right
Everything I've got By Jupiter
Exercise Lido Lady
Face the facts I Married an Angel
Factories -- mechanique The Valiant Years
Fair is fair NON-SHOW MUSIC
Fair trade I Remember Mama
Falling in love with love The Boys from Syracuse
Fam'ly we will be, A I Remember Mama
Fan tan fanny Flower Drum Song
Farmer and the cowman, The Oklahoma!
Father of the man NON-SHOW MUSIC
Father of the bride, The Lawrence of Arabia
Fellow needs a girl, A Allegro
Femme a toujours vingt ans!, La Ever Green
Ferrovius Androcles and the Lion
Fiddle and geetar Victory at Sea
Field of cloth of gold, The Rex
Flow on river NON-SHOW MUSIC
Flower garden of my heart, The Pal Joey
Flute and Chopin The Valiant Years
Fol-de-rol Cinderella
Follow in our footsteps Androcles and the Lion
Food for scandal Fools for Scandal
Fool meets fool By Jupiter
Forty nights Two by Two
France gay The Valiant Years
From afar Rex
From another world Higher and Higher
From Naples to Rome Victory at Sea
Gateway of the Temple of Minerva, The By Jupiter
Gavotte Cinderella
Gentlemen is a dope, The Allegro
Geraniums in the winder Carousel
German band The Valiant Years
German unison The Valiant Years
Getting married to a person Two by Two
Getting to know you South Pacific
Getting to know you The King and I
Giant calliope Jumbo
Gigolo The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Gilding the guild The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Girl friend, The The Girl Friend
Girl I love to leave behind, The Stage Door Canteen
Gitka's song, The Two by Two
Give it back to the Indians Too Many Girls
Give this little girl a hand Peggy-Ann
Glad to be unhappy Jumbo
Glad to be unhappy MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 10]
Gliding through my memoree Flower Drum Song
Go east Too Many Girls
Golden ram, The Two by Two
Good bad woman NON-SHOW MUSIC
Good fellow mine The Girl Friend
Good idea for Joe Allegro
Good provider NON-SHOW MUSIC
Grandma Allegro
Grant avenue Flower Drum Song
Great big town, A Pal Joey
Greeks have no word for it, The Higher and Higher
Greeks have no word for it, The The Boys from Syracuse
Guadalcanal march Victory at Sea
Gypsy dance NON-SHOW MUSIC
Happiest house on the block, The Pipe Dream
Happy Christmas, little friend NON-SHOW MUSIC
Happy hunting horn Pal Joey
Happy talk South Pacific
Harlemania Ever Green
Harmonia Ghost Town
Have you met Miss Jones? I'd Rather Be Right
He and she The Boys from Syracuse
He had twins! The Boys from Syracuse
He was the last rose of summer NON-SHOW MUSIC
He was too good to me Simple Simon
Heart us quicker than the eye, The On Your Toes
Heigh-ho, lackaday Dearest Enemy
Hello MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
Hello, young lovers The King and I
Henry Catherine scene Rex
Here comes the lion NON-SHOW MUSIC
Here we are again Do I Hear a Waltz?
Here's a hand By Jupiter
Hey, girlie Two by Two
Highest judge of all, The Carousel
His chances are not worth a penny I'd Rather Be Right
Hollywood party Hollywood Party
Home guard, The The Valiant Years
Homogeneous cabinet, A I'd Rather Be Right
Honey bun South Pacific
Honeymoon ballet Hollywood Party
How can love survive? The Sound of Music
How can you forget? Fools for Scandal
How do you bring up children? I Remember Mama
How long? Pipe Dream
How sad No Strings
How to win friends and influence people I Married an Angel
How's your health? Higher and Higher
Howdy, Broadway Peggy-Ann
Hum to The Girl Friend
Hundred million miracles, A Flower Drum Song
Hunting ballet Simple Simon
Hunting scene Simple Simon
Hunting song Simple Simon
Hymn of victory Victory at Sea
Hymn sort of, A The Valiant Years
I am a witch Pipe Dream
I am going to like it here Flower Drum Song
I brought you a gift Rex
I cain't say no Oklahoma!
I can't complain Two by Two
I could write a book Pal Joey
I didn't know what time it was Too Many Girls
I do not know a day I did not love you Two by Two
I don't know how I Remember Mama
I enjoy being a girl Flower Drum Song
I have confidence The Sound of Music
I have dreamed The King and I
I have let the time run on Allegro
I have loved and I've learned The Sound of Music
I haven't got a worry in the world Happy Birthday
I keep on singing Mississippi
I know it can happen again Allegro
I like to recognize the tune Too Many Girls
I love you more than yesterday Lady Fingers
I must love you MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
I must love you Chee-Chee
I remember Mama I Remember Mama
I still believe in you She's My Baby
I want a man MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 1]
I want a man America's Sweetheart
I want a man Lido Lady
I want to be a grocer The Chinese Lantern
I was there No Strings
I whistle a happy tune The King and I
I wish I were in love again Babes in Arms
I write, you read I Remember Mama
I'd like to take you home The Girl Friend
I'd like to take you home Bad Habits of 1925
I'd rather be right Fools for Scandal
I'd rather be right I'd Rather Be Right
I'll miss you Rex
I'll take a little of you on toast Let's Have Fun
I'll tell the man in the street I Married an Angel
I'm a fool, little one MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
I'm a queen in my own domain Hollywood Party
I'm broke You'll Never Know
I'm gonna wash that man right... South Pacific
I'm hard to please Follow Thru
I'm one of the boys Hollywood Party
I'm talking to my pal Pal Joey
I'm your girl Me and Juliet
I've got five dollars America's Sweetheart
I've got to get back to New York Hallelujah, I'm a Bum
Idylls of the king The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
If I give in to you Ever Green
If I loved you Carousel
If I were you Betsy
If I weren't king Cinderella
If the twig's bent Pal Joey
Imagine Babes in Arms
Impossible Cinderella
Impromptu song Ever Green
In a great big way MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
In Californ-I.A. America's Sweetheart
In my own little corner Cinderella
In the cool of the evening Ever Green
In the heart of a motorman NON-SHOW MUSIC
In time Rex
Innocent chorus girls of yesterday America's Sweetheart
Intermission talk Me and Juliet
Is it the uniform? MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Is my girl refined? Betsy
Is'nt it romantic? Love Me Tonight
Isn't it kinda fun? State Fair
It feels good Me and Juliet
It is not the end of the world I Remember Mama
It may rain The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
It might as well be spring State Fair
It never happened before Follow Thru
It's a darn nice campus Allegro
It's a grand night for singing State Fair
It's a scandal! It's a outrage! Oklahoma!
It's going to be good to be gone I Remember Mama
It's got to be love Jumbo
It's me Me and Juliet
It's pretty in the city Higher and Higher
It's the little things in Texas State Fair
Jack and Jill Say Mama
Jazz reception Heads Up!
Je m'en fiche du sex-appeal Ever Green
Johnny one note Babes in Arms
Jolly Churchill The Valiant Years
Jonathan I Picked a Daisy
Josi-Mosi theme see: Wiowani, Josi-Mosi, and Mee Mee themes
Joy spreader, The The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Jumping Jack! You'll Never Know
June is bustin' out all over Carousel
Jupiter forbid By Jupiter
Jury song The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Just a little lie You'll Never Know
Just a little souvenir The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Kansas City Oklahoma!
Keep 'em rolling! Keep 'Em Rolling
Keep away from the moonlight Hollywood Party
Keep it gay Me and Juliet
Keys to heaven The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Kings Rex
Kiss for Cinderella, A MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Kitzel engagement, The Betsy
Kralahome The King and I
La-la-la No Strings
Labor is the thing I'd Rather Be Right
Labor is the thing I Married an Angel
Ladies of the evening The Boys from Syracuse
Lady is a tramp, The Babes in Arms
Lady Luck is grinning Spring Is Here
Lady must live, A America's Sweetheart
Lady of heaven If I Were King
Land where the camp songs go, The NON-SHOW MUSIC
Landing Victory at Sea
Ländler The Sound of Music
Lars, Lars I Remember Mama
Last week the English Do I Hear a Waltz?
Laugh Jumbo
Lawrence theme Lawrence of Arabia
Laying the cornerstone Hallelujah, I'm a Bum
Let me walk! NON-SHOW MUSIC
Let's both go home and kiss our mothers A Connecticut Yankee
Let's sing a song about nothing Fools for Scandal
Lido lady MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
Life is unstable If I Were King
Life was monotonous By Jupiter
Life with Father By Jupiter
Life! Liberty! Higher and Higher
Like a god Flower Drum Song
Lion king, The Ever Green
Little birdie told me so, A MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
Little bit more, A I Remember Mama
Little girl blue Jumbo
Loads of love No Strings
Lolita They Met in Argentina
Lolita Pal Joey
Lonely goatherd, The The Sound of Music
Lonely room Oklahoma!
Lonely traveling man, A NON-SHOW MUSIC
Look no further No Strings
Look out! Too Many Girls
Lopsided bus, A Pipe Dream
Love knows best Fools for Scandal
Love like ours Hollywood Party
Love, look away Flower Drum Song
Love makes the world go No Strings
Love me tonight Love Me Tonight
Love never went to college Too Many Girls
Lovely day for a murder Higher and Higher
Lovely night, A Cinderella
Lover to lover Lawrence of Arabia
Lover to lover I Picked a Daisy
Lover! Love Me Tonight
Luftwaffe The Valiant Years
Lullaby I Remember Mama
Mah jong maid Bad Habits of 1925
Maine No Strings
Majestic England The Valiant Years
Make hey! Make hey! One Dam Thing After Another
Make way The Prisoner of Zenda
Mama always makes it better I Remember Mama
Man for me, The Love Me Tonight
Man I used to be, The Pipe Dream
Man who has everything, The No Strings
Manhattan The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Manny NON-SHOW MUSIC
Many a new day Oklahoma!
March of the royal Siamese children The King and I
March of the clowns Jumbo
Mare nostram The Valiant Years
Maria The Sound of Music
Marriage type love Me and Juliet
Maybe, maybe, maybe I Remember Mama
Me and Juliet Me and Juliet
Mee Mee theme see: Wiowani, Josi-Mosi, and Mee Mee themes
Melinda I Picked a Daisy
Melting pot, The NON-SHOW MUSIC
Melville NON-SHOW MUSIC
Memories of Madison Square Garden Jumbo
Mexico The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Michener Lawrence of Arabia
Mimi Love Me Tonight
Miners Ghost Town
Mister Snow Carousel
Mobody looks at the man Ever Green
Mom NON-SHOW MUSIC
Money isn't everything Allegro
Moon in my window Do I Hear a Waltz?
Moon of my delight MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Moonlight Mama The Melody Man
More I see of other girls, The Jumbo
More I see of other girls, The Mississippi
More than just a friend State Fair
Mormon Ghost Town
Morning is midnight MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
Morning's at seven Higher and Higher
Mosquito fleet The Valiant Years
Most beautiful girl in the world, The Jumbo
Most disagreeable man, A I Remember Mama
Mother and daughters' march Cinderella
Mountain greenery The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Mr. Director You'll Never Know
Music & the emotions The Play's the Thing
Music in you NON-SHOW MUSIC
My best love Flower Drum Song
My Clementine! NON-SHOW MUSIC
My daughter Rex
My favorite things The Sound of Music
My friend South Pacific
My friend the night Hollywood Party
My funny valentine Babes in Arms
My girl back home South Pacific
My heart is Sheba bound MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
My heart stood still MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
My hobby NON-SHOW MUSIC
My idiot's delight NON-SHOW MUSIC
My king can do no wrong The Prisoner of Zenda
My lord and master The King and I
My Prince Too Many Girls
My romance Jumbo
My sweet America's Sweetheart
My tent in Paradox NON-SHOW MUSIC
Never go to Argentina They Met in Argentina
Never say no to a man State Fair
Next time it happens, The Pipe Dream
Night was made for dancing, The Hollywood Party
Ninety again Two by Two
Ninety again Two by Two
No more waiting Androcles and the Lion
No place but home Ever Green
No song more pleasing Rex
No strings No Strings
No understand Do I Hear a Waltz?
No way to stop it The Sound of Music
Nobody told me No Strings
Nobody's heart By Jupiter
North America meets South America They Met in Argentina
Not so innocent fun I'd Rather Be Right
Nothing at all NON-SHOW MUSIC
Nothing but you Higher and Higher
Nothing to do but relax By Jupiter
Nothing's wrong A Connecticut Yankee
Now is the time South Pacific
Now you leave The King and I
Oh, dear! The Prisoner of Zenda
Oh, Diogenes The Boys from Syracuse
Oh, so lovely! Simple Simon
Oh, what a beautiful mornin' Oklahoma!
Oklahoma Oklahoma!
Olangtsi theme, and Mee Mee themes see: Wiowani, Josi-Mosi
Old city boy at heart, An I Remember Mama
Old enough to love Dearest Enemy
Old man, An Two by Two
On the Bahama NON-SHOW MUSIC
On the track They Met in Argentina
On your toes On Your Toes
Once I was young Fools for Scandal
One a day Winkle Town
One foot, other foot Allegro
One of us should be two Betsy
Ordinary couple, An The Sound of Music
Orthodox fool, An No Strings
Other generation, The Flower Drum Song
Our private olympic games On Your Toes
Our State Fair State Fair
Out of my dreams Oklahoma!